A Guide to the Episcopal Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1905-1990
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Jerusalem and the East Mission (199) 1930 (Box-folder 32-19)
- Bishop Jett--personal (200) 1930 (Box-folder 32-20)
- Bishop Jett's tenth anniversary of consecration (200A) 1930 (Box-folder 32-21)
- Bishop Jett's anniversary--correspondence (200B) 1930 (Box-folder 32-22)
- Journal--appendices (201) 1930 (Box-folder 32-23)
- Journal--the Bishop's address (202); Journal--copy (203); Journal--minutes (204) 1930 (Box-folder 32-24)
- Journal--mailing list (205) 1930 (Box-folder 32-25)
- Journal--publisher (206); Lambeth Conference (206A); Lay Readers (207) 1930 (Box-folder 32-26)
- Layman's League (208) 1930 (Box-folder 32-27)
- Letters Dimissory (210) 1930 (Box-folder 32-28)
- National Council--Department of Missions (221); National Council--Department of Publicity (222) 1930 (Box-folder 32-29)
- National Council--Department of Religious Education (223) 1930 (Box-folder 32-30)
- National Council--Department of Social Service (224) 1930 (Box-folder 32-31)
- National Council--treasurer (226) 1930 (Box-folder 32-32)
- Box 33 1930-33
- News Notes (229); Notes (230) 1930 (Box-folder 33-1)
- Ordination Certificates (231A); Pastoral Letters (231B); Prayer Book (234) 1930 (Box-folder 33-2)
- Province of Washington--deaf mutes (235); Province of Washington--general (236); Province of Washington--synod (237) 1930 (Box-folder 33-3)
- Railways--transportation (238) 1930 (Box-folder 33-4)
- Receipts (239) 1930 (Box-folder 33-5)
- Receipts for checks--numbers 7378 to 7700 (239) 1930 (Box-folder 33-6)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (240); Savin, Williams (240A) 1930 (Box-folder 33-7)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (242) 1930 (Box-folder 33-8)
- Standing Committee (244); Stuart Hall (245) 1930 (Box-folder 33-9)
- Taylor, Gordon L. (246); Theological Seminary (247) 1930 (Box-folder 33-10)
- Treasurer of Diocese (248) 1930 (Box-folder 33-11)
- Trustees of Diocese (249) 1930 (Box-folder 33-12)
- Vestrices (250) 1930 (Box-folder 33-13)
- Virginia Episcopal (251) 1930 (Box-folder 33-14)
- Virginia Episcopal School Endowment (251A) 1930 (Box-folder 33-15)
- Virginia Summer Conference of Religious Education (252) 1930 (Box-folder 33-16)
- Virginia Summer Conference of Religious Education (252) 1930 (Box-folder 33-17)
- Visitations (253) 1930 (Box-folder 33-18)
- Volunteer Workers (253A); The Witness (255); Women's Auxiliary--Diocesan (256) 1930 (Box-folder 33-19)
- Women Workers (257) 1930 (Box-folder 33-20)
- Young, H.H. (258); Young People (259) 1930 (Box-folder 33-21)
- #317 1930 (Box-folder 33-22)
- Lambert's Point Tow Boat file (317) 1930 (Box-folder 33-23)
- Piney Mission (317) 1930 (Box-folder 33-24)
- Reverend L.O. Forqueran 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-25)
- Portland Lots 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-26)
- Norton--All Saints (71); Norwood--Christ (72); Pearisburg--Christ (73); Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (74) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-27)
- Reverend Norvin C. Duncan (148) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-28)
- Henry H. Martens (148) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-29)
- Reverend John H. Oldham (148) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-30)
- Conference--executive secretaries (151A) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-31)
- Miller, Fredk. H. (214A) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-32)
- Wilson, John A. (254) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-33)
- Church Pension Fund (318) 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-34)
- Council--parochial (165); Council--program (166) 1930-32 (Box-folder 33-35)
- Communion Wine (150) 1930-33 (Box-folder 33-36)
- Box 34 1931
- Accountant's Report 1931 (Box-folder 34-1)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2); Altavista--St. Andrew's (3); Altavist--St. Peter's (5) 1931 (Box-folder 34-2)
- Amherst--Ascension (6); Amherst--Christ Mission (7); Arrington--Trinity (9) 1931 (Box-folder 34-3)
- Bastian (10A); Bedford--St. John's (11); Bedford--St. Philips (12) 1931 (Box-folder 34-4)
- Bedford--St. Philip's--correspondence relevant to rectory, tenant, etc. (12) 1931 (Box-folder 34-5)
- Big Island--St. Thomas (13); Big Stone Gap--Christ (14); Blacksburg--Christ (15) 1931 (Box-folder 34-6)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (16); Boonesboro--Trinity (17); Bristol--Emmanuel (18) 1931 (Box-folder 34-7)
- Brookneal (19); Buchanan--Grace (20); Buchanan--Trinity (21) 1931 (Box-folder 34-8)
- Buena Vista--Christ (22); Gallay--St. Peter's (24) 1931 (Box-folder 34-9)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (26); Clintwood (29A); Covington--Emmanuel (31) 1931 (Box-folder 34-10)
- Covington--Grace Mission (32); Dante--St. Mark's (34); Drill--Mission (35) 1931 (Box-folder 34-11)
- Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (37); Endicott--St. John's (38) 1931 (Box-folder 34-12)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (39); Evington--Good Shepherd (40); Fincastle--St. Mark's (41) 1931 (Box-folder 34-13)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (42); Forest--Ivy Chapel (43); Forest--St. Stephen's (44) 1931 (Box-folder 34-14)
- Glade Spring--Grace (45); Gladys--Christ (40); Glasgow--St. John's (48); Hot Springs--St. Luke's (50) 1931 (Box-folder 34-15)
- Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (51); Ivanhoe--St. Barnabas (52); Jervell Ridge (53); Lebanon--Mission (54) 1931 (Box-folder 34-16)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (55); Low Moor--Union Church (56); Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (57) 1931 (Box-folder 34-17)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (58); Lynchburg--St. John's (60); Lynchburg--St. Paul's (61) 1931 (Box-folder 34-18)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel (62); Marion--Christ (63) 1931 (Box-folder 34-19)
- Martinsville--Christ (64); Massies Mill--Grace (65); Montvale--St. Mark's (67) 1931 (Box-folder 34-20)
- Narrows (68); Nora--St. Stephen's (70) 1931 (Box-folder 34-21)
- Pocahontas--Christ (75); Pounding Mill Mission (76); Pulaski--Christ (77) 1932 (Box-folder 34-22)
- Radford--Grace (78); Richland--Trinity (79); Roanoke--Christ (80) 1931 (Box-folder 34-23)
- Roanoke--St. John's (81); Roanoke--St. Luke's (81A) 1931 (Box-folder 34-24)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (82) 1931 (Box-folder 34-25)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (83); Rustburg--Trinity (84); St. Paul--Grace House (85) 1931 (Box-folder 34-26)
- St. Paul--Sandy Ridge (86); Salem--Mt. Gerizim (87); Salem--St. Paul's (88); Saltville--St. Paul's (89) 1931 (Box-folder 34-27)
- Schuyler--Christ (91); Six Mile Bridge--Grace (92) 1931 (Box-folder 34-28)
- Splashdam--Mission (93) 1931 (Box-folder 34-29)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (94); Staunton--Trinity (95); Stratton--Mission (96) 1931 (Box-folder 34-30)
- Sweet Briar (97); Sweet Chalybeate Springs (98); Tazewell--Stras Memorial (99) 1931 (Box-folder 34-31)
- Box 35 1931
- Tom's Creek--Mission (100); Verona--Emmanuel Chapel (101); Waynesboro--St. John's (103) 1931 (Box-folder 35-1)
- Wilder--Mission (104); Wytheville--St. John (106); Yards--St. Paul (107) 1931 (Box-folder 35-2)
- A--general (108); B--general (109) 1931 (Box-folder 35-3)
- C--general (110) 1931 (Box-folder 35-4)
- D--general (111); E--general (112); F--general (113) 1931 (Box-folder 35-5)
- G--general (114); H--general (115); I--general (116) 1931 (Box-folder 35-6)
- J--general (117); K--general (118); L--general (119) 1931 (Box-folder 35-7)
- M--general (120); N--general (121); O--general (122); P & Q--general (123) 1931 (Box-folder 35-8)
- R--general (124); S--general (125); T--general (126); U & V--general (127) 1931 (Box-folder 35-9)
- W--general (1931: 128); Advance Work (1931: 130) 1931 (Box-folder 35-10)
- American Church Building Fund Commission (132); American Church Institute for Negroes (133); Appeals (133A) 1931 (Box-folder 35-11)
- Associate Missions (134) 1931 (Box-folder 35-12)
- Automobiles (134A) 1931 (Box-folder 35-13)
- Marshall Bacot (134B); Bleasley, R.R. (136) 1931 (Box-folder 35-14)
- Birthday Thank Offering (137A); Bishop's Discretionary Fund (138); Bishop Payne--Divinity School (139) 1931 (Box-folder 35-15)
- Board of Church Finance (140); Boys' Home--Covington (141) 1931 (Box-folder 35-16)
- Francis Burks (141A); Chancellor (142); Charges to be reimbursed (142A); Church Army (142B) 1931 (Box-folder 35-17)
- Church at Work (143); Church Pension Fund (144); Church Properties--Fire Insurance Corporation (144A) 1931 (Box-folder 35-18)
- Church School Lenten Offering (145) 1931 (Box-folder 35-19)
- Clergy Conference (146A); Communion wine (150); Consents (151) 1931 (Box-folder 35-20)
- Inquiries for ministry positions (148) 1931 (Box-folder 35-21)
- Inquiries for ministry positions (B; G; H; P; R, 148) 1931 (Box-folder 35-22)
- Elliott B. Meredith (148, 215) 1931 (Box-folder 35-23)
- Convocations (152); Church Council Property (155); Clerical Council Support (156) 1931 (Box-folder 35-24)
- Constitution and Canons Council (157); Elections and Credentials Council (159) 1931 (Box-folder 35-25)
- Council Program (166) 1931 (Box-folder 35-26)
- Council--general (160); Increase of the Ministry Council (161); Council--minutes (162) 1931 (Box-folder 35-27)
- Council--reports (166A) 1931 (Box-folder 35-28)
- Council--rural committee (166B); Council Secretary (167); State of the Church Council (168) 1931 (Box-folder 35-29)
- Daughters of the King (169); Depositions (170); Diocesan Records (171) 1931 (Box-folder 35-30)
- Diocesan Mission School (172) 1931 (Box-folder 35-31)
- Diocesan Office (173); Mr. Donald Durant (176A) 1931 (Box-folder 35-32)
- Episcopal High School (177); Episcopal Residence (178); Evangelism--Diocesan (179) 1931 (Box-folder 35-33)
- Examining Chaplains (181); Executive Secreties Conference (181A); Executive Board--field department (182) 1931 (Box-folder 35-34)
- Field Department--pledges (183A) 1931 (Box-folder 35-35)
- Box 36 1931
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (184); Executive Board--Department of Publicity (185) 1931 (Box-folder 36-1)
- Executive Board--Department of Religious Education (186); Religious Education Director (186A); Executive Board--Department of Social Science (187) 1931 (Box-folder 36-2)
- Executive Board--general (188) 1931 (Box-folder 36-3)
- Federal Council of Churches (191); First National Exchange Bank (192) 1931 (Box-folder 36-4)
- General Convention (193) 1931 (Box-folder 36-5)
- General Convention (193) 1931 (Box-folder 36-6)
- General Convention (193) 1931 (Box-folder 36-7)
- General Convention (193) 1931 (Box-folder 36-8)
- General Convention--"placement of clergy" (193) 1931 (Box-folder 36-9)
- General Convention--travel (193B) 1931 (Box-folder 36-10)
- General Convention--hotels (193A); General Convention--House of Bishops (194); Girls Friendly Society (195) 1931 (Box-folder 36-11)
- Doctor Glazebrook (195A) 1931 (Box-folder 36-12)
- Reverend H.H. Hemming--Big Stone Gap (196A); Historiographer (197); Industrial Work (197A) 1931 (Box-folder 36-13)
- Insurance (198); Jerusalem and East Mission (199); Jett, R.C.--personal (200) 1931 (Box-folder 36-14)
- Journal--Bishop's Address (202) 1931 (Box-folder 36-15)
- Journal--copy (203); Journal--minutes (204) 1931 (Box-folder 36-16)
- Journal--mailing list (205) 1931 (Box-folder 36-17)
- Journal--publisher (206) 1931 (Box-folder 36-18)
- Lantern Slides (206A) 1931 (Box-folder 36-19)
- Lay Readers (207); Laymen's League (208) 1931 (Box-folder 36-20)
- Letcher, John D. (209); Letters Dimissory (210) 1931 (Box-folder 36-21)
- Library (211); Mr. A.H. Light--Evington, Virginia (1931: 211A) 1931 (Box-folder 36-22)
- Living Church (212); Living Church Annual (213) 1931 (Box-folder 36-23)
- Mimeograph and Circular Letters (215); Morehouse Publishing Company (216) 1931 (Box-folder 36-24)
- National Council--presiding bishop (218) 1931 (Box-folder 36-25)
- National Council--Field Department (219) 1931 (Box-folder 36-26)
- National Council--Department of Missions (221) 1931 (Box-folder 36-27)
- National Council--Publicity Department (222) 1931 (Box-folder 36-28)
- National Council--Religious Education Department (223); National Council--Social Service Department (224) 1931 (Box-folder 36-29)
- National Council--treasurer (226) 1931 (Box-folder 36-30)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (227) 1931 (Box-folder 36-31)
- News Notes (229) 1931 (Box-folder 36-32)
- Notes (230); Prayer Book (234) 1931 (Box-folder 36-33)
- Province of Washington--deaf mutes (235); Province of Washington--general (226) 1931 (Box-folder 36-34)
- Province of Washington--general (236) 1931 (Box-folder 36-35)
- Province of Washington--synod (237); Railways and Transportation (238) 1931 (Box-folder 36-36)
- Receipts (239) 1931 (Box-folder 36-37)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (240); Mrs. William J. Smith (240A) 1931 (Box-folder 36-38)
- Southern Churchman (241) 1931 (Box-folder 36-39)
- Box 37 1931-48
- Southwestern Episcopalian (242) 1931 (Box-folder 37-1)
- Standing Committee (244); Stuart Hall (245) 1931 (Box-folder 37-2)
- Stuart Hall (245) 1931 (Box-folder 37-3)
- Student Supply (245B) 1931 (Box-folder 37-4)
- Theological Seminary (247) 1931 (Box-folder 37-5)
- Theological Seminary--Alexandria, Virginia (247) 1931 (Box-folder 37-6)
- Theological Seminary--"Deanship" (247A) 1931 (Box-folder 37-7)
- Treasurer of Diocese (248) 1931 (Box-folder 37-8)
- Trustees of Diocese (249) 1931 (Box-folder 37-9)
- Vestries (250) 1931 (Box-folder 37-10)
- Virginia Episcopal School (251) 1931 (Box-folder 37-11)
- Virginia Summer School (252) 1931 (Box-folder 37-12)
- Visitations (253) 1931 (Box-folder 37-13)
- Visitations (253) 1931 (Box-folder 37-14)
- Witness (255) 1931 (Box-folder 37-15)
- Woman's Auxiliary Diocese (256) 1931 (Box-folder 37-16)
- Women's Auxiliary--general (256A) 1931 (Box-folder 37-17)
- Women Workers (257) 1931 (Box-folder 37-18)
- Young, Reverend H.H. (258) 1931 (Box-folder 37-19)
- President's Statements (303) 1931 (Box-folder 37-20)
- Boys' Home--Covington (304) 1931 (Box-folder 37-21)
- #317 1931 (Box-folder 37-22)
- Lambert's Point Tow Boat File (317) 1931 (Box-folder 37-23)
- Operation of Diocesan Automobiles (317) 1931 (Box-folder 37-24)
- Treasurer's Correspondence (317) 1931 (Box-folder 37-25)
- General Convention Matters (322) 1931 (Box-folder 37-26)
- Council Bulletin, Clerical Support, Pension Fund and Mission Fund 1931-32 (Box-folder 37-27)
- P-Q--general (123); R--general (124); S--general (125) 1931-32 (Box-folder 37-28)
- Reverend Paul Due (148) 1931-32 (Box-folder 37-29)
- Clarence H. Lake (148) 1931-32 (Box-folder 37-30)
- Reverend R. Bayard Proctor (148) 1931-32 (Box-folder 37-31)
- St. Mary's Church--Basic (Waynesboro, Virginia, 317) 1931-32 (Box-folder 37-32)
- Council--minutes and papers (319) 1931-32 (Box-folder 37-33)
- Reverend William J. Alfriend 1931-33 (Box-folder 37-34)
- Wytheville Hotel Corporation (317) 1931-33 (Box-folder 37-35)
- Reverend Walter V. Reed (148) 1931-34 (Box-folder 37-36)
- Stuart Hall--building fund bank book (216) 1931-48 (Box-folder 37-37)
- Accountant's Report 1932 (Box-folder 37-38)
- Diocesan Council 1932 (Box-folder 37-39)
- Morehouse Publishing 1932 (Box-folder 37-40)
- Pastoral Letters 1932 (Box-folder 37-41)
- Pension Fund 1932 (Box-folder 37-42)
- Reverend John Ridout 1932 (Box-folder 37-43)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1932 (Box-folder 37-44)
- Altavista--St. Andrew's (4); Abingdon--St. Thomas' (2) 1932 (Box-folder 37-45)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1932 (Box-folder 37-46)
- Amherst--Ascension (6); Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (7); Aappalachia--Grace (8) 1932 (Box-folder 37-47)
- Arrington--Trinity (9); Bastian Mission (10A) 1932 (Box-folder 37-48)
- Box 38 1932
- Bedford--St. John's (11); Bedford--St. Philip's (12); Big Island--St. Thomas' (13) 1932 (Box-folder 38-1)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ (14); Blacksburg--Christ (15) 1932 (Box-folder 38-2)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (16); Boonsboro--Trinity (17); Bristol--Emmanuel (18) 1932 (Box-folder 38-3)
- Brookneal (19); Buchanan--Grace (20); Buchanan--Trinity (21) 1932 (Box-folder 38-4)
- Buena Vista--Christ (22); Byllesby--Mission (23); Gallaway--St. Peter's (24) 1932 (Box-folder 38-5)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas' (26); Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (28) 1932 (Box-folder 38-6)
- Clintwood (29A); Covington--Emmanuel (31) 1932 (Box-folder 38-7)
- Covington--Grace Mission (32); Dante--St. Mark's (34) 1932 (Box-folder 38-8)
- Drill--Mission (35); Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (37); Endicott--St. John's (38) 1932 (Box-folder 38-9)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (39); Evington--Our Saviour (40); Fincastle--St. Mark's (41) 1932 (Box-folder 38-10)
- Follymills--Good Shepherd (42); Forest--Ivy Chapel (43); Forest--St. Stephen's (44) 1932 (Box-folder 38-11)
- Glade Spring--Grace (45); Gladys--Christ Church (46); Glasgow--St. John's (48) 1932 (Box-folder 38-12)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (50); Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (51); Ivanhoe--St. Barnabas (52) 1932 (Box-folder 38-13)
- Jewell Ridge--Mission (52A); Lebanon--Mission (54); Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (55) 1932 (Box-folder 38-14)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (57); Lynchburg--Grace (58) 1932 (Box-folder 38-15)
- Reverend William G. Pendleton (58, 148) 1932 (Box-folder 38-16)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (60); Lynchburg--St. Paul's (61); Madison Heights--Emmanuel (62); Marion-- Christ (63) 1932 (Box-folder 38-17)
- Martinsville--Christ (64); Masies Mill (65) 1932 (Box-folder 38-18)
- Merrimac Mines--Mission (66); Montvale--St. Mark's (67) 1932 (Box-folder 38-19)
- Natural Bridge Station--Trinity (69); Nora--St. Stephen's (70) 1932 (Box-folder 38-20)
- Norton--All Saints (71); Norwood--Christ (72) 1932 (Box-folder 38-21)
- Pearisburg--Christ (73); Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (74) 1932 (Box-folder 38-22)
- Pounding Mill--Mission (76) 1932 (Box-folder 38-23)
- Pulaski--Christ (77) 1932 (Box-folder 38-24)
- Radford--Grace (78) 1932 (Box-folder 38-25)
- Radford--Reverend James A. Figg (78) 1932 (Box-folder 38-26)
- Richlands--Trinity (79) 1932 (Box-folder 38-27)
- Roanoke--Christ (80) 1932 (Box-folder 38-28)
- Roanoke--St. John's (81) 1932 (Box-folder 38-29)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (82) 1932 (Box-folder 38-30)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (83) 1932 (Box-folder 38-31)
- St. Paul--Grace House-on-the-mountain (1932: 85) 1932 (Box-folder 38-32)
- Salem--Mt. Gerizim (87); Salem--St. Paul's (88) 1932 (Box-folder 38-33)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (89); Saltville--Matthew's Memorial (90) 1932 (Box-folder 38-34)
- Schuyler--Christ (91) 1932 (Box-folder 38-35)
- Six Mile Bridge--Grace (92); Splashdam--Mission (93) 1932 (Box-folder 38-36)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (94) 1932 (Box-folder 38-37)
- Staunton--Trinity (95); Sweet Briar (97) 1932 (Box-folder 38-38)
- Sweet Chalybeate--Forrest Memorial (98); Tazewell--Stras Memorial (99) 1932 (Box-folder 38-39)
- Tom's Creek--Mission (100); Waynesboro--St. John's (103) 1932 (Box-folder 38-40)
- Wytheville--St. John's (106); Yards--St. Paul's (107) 1932 (Box-folder 38-41)
- A--general (108) 1932 (Box-folder 38-42)
- B--general (109) 1932 (Box-folder 38-43)
- Box 39 1932
- C--general (110) 1932 (Box-folder 39-1)
- D--general (111); E--general (112) 1932 (Box-folder 39-2)
- F--general (113) 1932 (Box-folder 39-3)
- G--general (114) 1932 (Box-folder 39-4)
- H--general (115); I--general (116); J--general (117); K--general (118) 1932 (Box-folder 39-5)
- L--general (119); M--general (120); N--general (121) 1932 (Box-folder 39-6)
- O--general (122); T--general (126); U & V--general (127); W--general (128) 1932 (Box-folder 39-7)
- X & Y & Z--general (129); Deaconess Adams (129A); Advance Work (130) 1932 (Box-folder 39-8)
- American Church Building Fund Committee (132); American Church Institute for Negroes (133); Appeals (133A) 1932 (Box-folder 39-9)
- Associate Mission (134) 1932 (Box-folder 39-10)
- Automobile (134A); Marshall Bacot (134B); Beasley, Richard R. (136) 1932 (Box-folder 39-11)
- Birthday Thank Offering (137A); Bishop's Discretionary Fund (138); Bishop Payne--Divinity School (139) 1932 (Box-folder 39-12)
- Board of Church Finance (140) 1932 (Box-folder 39-13)
- Boys' Home--Covington (141) 1932 (Box-folder 39-14)
- Frances Burks (141A) 1932 (Box-folder 39-15)
- Miss Nancy G. Chamberlain--Dante, Virginia (141B); Chancellor of Diocese (142) 1932 (Box-folder 39-16)
- Church Pension Fund (144) 1932 (Box-folder 39-17)
- Church Properties--Fire Insurance Corporation (144A); Pageant--"The Bread of Life"--Lent 1932 (Box-folder 39-18)
- Church School Lenten Offering (145) 1932 (Box-folder 39-19)
- Churchman--New York (146); Clergy Conference (146A) 1932 (Box-folder 39-20)
- Reverend A. Campbell Tucker (148) 1932 (Box-folder 39-21)
- Inquiries for ministry Positions (B; C; D; G; H, 148) 1932 (Box-folder 39-22)
- Inquiries for ministry positions (A; J; K; L; M; N; P, 148) (Box-folder 39-23)
- Clergy for temporary work in diocese (148A); Communion Wine (150); Consents (151) 1932 (Box-folder 39-24)
- Conference of Executive Secretaries (151A); Convocation (152) 1932 (Box-folder 39-25)
- Council--Church Property (155); Council--Clerical Support (156) 1932 (Box-folder 39-26)
- Council--constitution and canons (157) 1932 (Box-folder 39-27)
- Council--elections and credentials (159) 1932 (Box-folder 39-28)
- Council--endowment by request (159A); Evaluation Committee (159B) 1932 (Box-folder 39-29)
- Council--general (160) 1932 (Box-folder 39-30)
- Council--increase of ministry (161); Council--minutes (161); Council--Missionary Night (163) 1932 (Box-folder 39-31)
- Council--new parishes and missions (164) 1932 (Box-folder 39-32)
- Council--reports (166A) 1932 (Box-folder 39-33)
- Rural Work Commission (166A); Council--Secretary (167); Daughters of the King (169) 1932 (Box-folder 39-34)
- Daughters of the King (169); Depositions (170); Diocesan Records (171) 1932 (Box-folder 39-35)
- Diocesan Mission School (172); Diocesan office (173) 1932 (Box-folder 39-36)
- Du Bose Memorial--Church Training School (176); Miss Julia Edwards (176A) 1932 (Box-folder 39-37)
- Episcopal High School (177); Evangelism--general church (180) 1932 (Box-folder 39-38)
- Examining Chaplains (181); Executive Board--Field Department (182) 1932 (Box-folder 39-39)
- Field Department--pledges for 1932 (183) (Box-folder 39-40)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (184) 1932 (Box-folder 39-41)
- Box 40 1932
- Executive Board--Department of Publicity (185); Executive Board--Department of Religious Education (186); Executive Board--Department of Social Science (187) 1932 (Box-folder 40-1)
- Executive Board--general (188) 1932 (Box-folder 40-2)
- Executive Board--Bishop's Attention (189); Federal Council of Churches (191); First National Exchange Bank (192) 1932 (Box-folder 40-3)
- General Church Deficit (192A) 1932 (Box-folder 40-4)
- General Convention (193); General Convention--House of Bishops (194) 1932 (Box-folder 40-5)
- Good Friday Offering (195A); Frank Hearns, Jr. (196A); Industrial Work (197A) 1932 (Box-folder 40-6)
- Insurance (198) 1932 (Box-folder 40-7)
- Jerusalem and East Mission (199) 1932 (Box-folder 40-8)
- Bishop Jett--personal (200) 1932 (Box-folder 40-9)
- Joint Diocesan Paper (200A) 1932 (Box-folder 40-10)
- Journal--Bishop's Address (202) 1932 (Box-folder 40-11)
- Journal--copy (203) 1932 (Box-folder 40-12)
- Journal--mailing list (205) 1932 (Box-folder 40-13)
- Journal--publisher (206) 1932 (Box-folder 40-14)
- Kanuga Lake Conferences (206A); Laymen's League (208); T.J. Leek (208A) 1932 (Box-folder 40-15)
- Notes--bank (209) 1932 (Box-folder 40-16)
- Letcher--John D. (209); Letters Dimissory (210); Library (11) 1932 (Box-folder 40-17)
- Living Church (212); Living Church Annual (213) 1932 (Box-folder 40-18)
- Mimeograph and circular letters (215); National Council--presiding Bishop (218) 1932 (Box-folder 40-19)
- Motion Pictures (216A) 1932 (Box-folder 40-20)
- National Council--Field Department (219) 1932 (Box-folder 40-21)
- National Council--Department of Missions (221) 1932 (Box-folder 40-22)
- National Council--Publicity Department (222) 1932 (Box-folder 40-23)
- National Council--Department of Religious Education (223) 1932 (Box-folder 40-24)
- National Council--Social Service Department (224) 1932 (Box-folder 40-25)
- National Council--Speakers' Bureau (225) 1932 (Box-folder 40-26)
- National Council--Treasurer (226) 1932 (Box-folder 40-27)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (227) 1932 (Box-folder 40-28)
- News Notes (229) 1932 (Box-folder 40-29)